人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：西蘭花小小姐  3CC醉芝士  Ethan-澤生
翻譯：威廉  一不二  韓小冰的非小燕  蘇慕晴天
來點甜蜜的我不介意
I sure could go for something sweet.
你要吃點什么嗎
Do you want to grab a bite to eat?
我想要的甜蜜不是吃的
Actually, it's not food that I'm craving.
怎么了
What? Is it...
不不  沒什么
No, no. It's nothing.
不  我恰好是"沒什么"專家
No, no. I happen to be an expert on nothing.
這個表情  可不是沒什么
And this. This is not nothing.
好吧
Okay. Fine.
-你知道你會說夢話對嗎  -嗯
- Do you know how you talk in your sleep sometimes? - Oh, yeah.
昨晚你說了個名字
Well, last night you said a name.
我猜不是你的名字
Oh... and not your name I'm assuming.
不是
No.
隨便說了個名字  別多想嘛
Well, I wouldn't read anything into one random utterance.
說了14遍
14 utterances.
名字是喬丹
And the name was Jordan.
你說了一遍又一遍
You said it over and over again.
喬丹是誰
Who's Jordan?
我不知道
I have no idea.
是女人嗎
Is it a woman?
不  沒什么
No, it's nothing.
卡塞爾  我知道"沒什么"
Castle, I know nothing.
"沒什么"是我親愛的朋友
Nothing is a dear friend of mine.
這個可不是"沒什么"
And this. This is not nothing.
是沒什么  而且
Yes, it is. Besides...
我大多數的話都毫無意義
Most of what I say is meaningless.
更何況是夢話呢
Why would it be any different when I'm asleep?
這事沒完
We're not done here.
得了  卡塞爾  喬丹是誰
Come on, castle. Who is Jordan?
我沒什么可隱瞞的  本來就沒什么可說的
I got nothing to hide. There's just nothing to tell.
那你怎么這么戒備
Then why are you being so defensive?
我沒有
I'm not.
好吧
Okay, fine.
那我等到你睡著好了
I'll just wait until you're asleep.
然后我再問你
And then I'll ask you.
你不能這樣做
You can't do that.
拜托  卡塞爾  你才說你沒什么可隱瞞的
Come on, Castle. You just said that you had nothing to hide.
在我睡著時審問我
Yeah, but interrogating me in my sleep?
你會用這么卑鄙的招數嗎
Would you stoop that low?
誰說我沒用過
Who says I haven't already?
早啊  蕾妮
Hey, Lanie.
哇  真是死在巧克力上啊
Wow. Talk about death by chocolate.
不關巧克力的事  卡塞爾
Don't blame it on the chocolate, castle.
死因是子彈
A bullet's what did him in.
那紅色的不是覆盆子醬嘍
So that red stuff's not raspberry sauce?
恐怕不是  子彈射出傷
Afraid not. Exit wound.
那么他是背后中槍然后跌進桶里
So he was shot in the back and then fell in the mixer?
看起來是的  但在那之前
Looks like, but before that,
他可能和兇手搏斗過
he may have struggled with his attacker.
米黃色纖維
Beige fibers--
在他的表帶上發現的
They were caught on his watchband.
鑒證組會拿去分析
C.S.U. will run an analysis.
被害人叫吉米·韋蘭  這家店的老板
Vic's name is Jimmy Whelan. He's the owner of the shop.
他沒有前科
He has no record...
從背景資料中也看不出誰可能是兇手
And nothing in his bio that points to who did this.
可以排除不滿意的顧客
You can rule out dissatisfied customers.
這些東西太好吃了
These things are insanely good.
你居然吃死人的紙杯蛋糕
You're eating a dead man's cupcake?
那邊有免費樣品
There was free samples.
死亡時間
Time of death?
11點半到12點
Between 11:30 and 12:00.
怎么看出來的
Based on what?
你一下子成了法醫嗎
All of a sudden, you're an M.E.?
你不是喜歡我扮醫生嗎
I thought you liked it when I played doctor.
這樣說的依據是
I, uh, based the time of death on what
死者助手的話
the vic's assistant told me.
就在那邊
Right over there.
托德   告訴我們發生了什么事
Okay, Todd, why don't you just run us through what happened?
吉米讓我11點半去送貨
Jimmy sent me on a delivery at 11:30--
送一打紅絲絨蛋糕到路口的美容院
A dozen red velvets to a beauty shop down the way.
我回來后發現
And when I came back...
吉米是個非常好的人
He's a super-nice guy-- Jimmy.
他認識的人中有沒有不這么想的
Well, is there anyone in his life who didn't feel that way?
我不清楚
I'm not sure.
我才在這里工作兩周
The truth is, this is only my second week here.
但我離開前他的表現很奇怪
But he was acting real strange right before I left.
怎么奇怪
Strange how?
店外有輛徘徊的車
This car... cruised by the shop,
開得很慢
kinda slow.
他變得緊張
He got all nervous.
那時他就讓我離開
That's when he sent me on my run,
好像是故意要支開我
like he wanted to get rid of me.
什么樣的車
What kind of car was it?
黑色的68年道奇突擊者
It was a black '68 charger r/t.
我比較懂大馬力車
I know my muscle cars.
看到司機了嗎
Did you see who was driving?
沒  我離開時  司機把車停到了街角
No, but whoever it was parked it around the corner as I was leaving.
我回來后  車開走了
When I got back, the car was gone,
吉米死了
And there was Jimmy.
我們需要那輛車的詳細描述
Well, we'll need a detailed description of that car.
看來吉米放了不少現金[面團]啊
Looks like Jimmy kept a lot of dough around here.
這里是西點店嘛
It is a bakery.
真好笑
Good one.
箱子是在他辦公室找到的
This briefcase was stashed in his office.
五萬現金
That's $50,000.
四塊錢一個蛋糕
Whoa. At $4 a pop,
得賣12500個
he would have to sell 12,500 cupcakes.
聽起來不太可能
That seems unlikely.
托德  你知道這筆錢嗎
Todd, what do you know about that money?
不知道  我發誓
Nothing. I swear.
但他對這個箱子非常緊張
But he's real paranoid about that case.
一周兩次  他會從保險柜里拿出來
Twice a week, he'd take it out of the safe
帶去斯坦頓島
and take it with him down to staten island.
-去做什么  -他說在那里有生意
- What for? - Just said he had business there.
顯然吉米做的不僅僅是紙杯蛋糕的生意
Well, obviously Jimmy was into more than just baking cupcakes.
調查市內所有
So let's look at all the owners
68年道奇突擊者車的車主
of '68 chargers in the metro area.
沒問題
You got it.
萊恩在哪里
Hey, where's Ryan?
對了
Oh, right.
和羅森伯格醫生約在20分鐘后
The appointment at dr. Rosenberg's office is in 20 minutes.
要15分鐘才能到
It's gonna take us at least 15 to get there,
我們應該出發了
So we should probably go, right?
這就是說你應該
Which means you should probably...
怎么了
Hey, what's the matter?
如果是我的問題呢
What if it's my fault?
如果結果是我有什么問題呢
What if it turns out that there's something wrong with me?
這不是任何人的錯  凱文
It's nobody's fault, Kev.
我們只是需要知道到底是怎么回事
We just need to know what's going on.
需要幫忙嗎
You want some help?
不錯
Nice.
烘焙大師吉米·韋蘭
So master baker Jimmy Whelan,
多年來售賣高熱量的美味烘焙食物
longtime purveyor of caloric yet delicious baked goods,
當地街區少年壘球隊的贊助人
sponsor of a local kids' softball team,
小生意圓桌會議的發起人
charter member of the small business roundtable--
但他怎么會有五萬現金
But what was he doing with 50 grand in cash,
還要秘密前往斯坦頓島
and why the secret trips to staten island?
聽起來有秘密的不止你一個人  卡塞爾
Sounds like you're not the only one keeping secrets, Castle.
我準備忽略這句話
I'm going to ignore that.
這很奇怪
That's peculiar.
這有什么好奇怪的
What's so peculiar about wanting to ignore--
不是  我是說這些采購單
No, no, no, I mean these purchase orders.
這里寫著吉米花了七萬多
They show that Jimmy spent over $70,000
買廚房設備
on kitchen equipment.
比如說六米多寬的小型冷庫
Like a 20-foot-wide walk-in freezer.
我好像沒見過那東西
I don't remember seeing that.
因為根本就沒有
That's because there wasn't one.
他廚房根本就放不下
It wouldn't even fit in his kitchen.
我查過那輛道奇車
Yo. So I ran '68 chargers.
城里只有幾輛這款車  不過聽好了
There's only a handful of them on the road, but get this.
其中有一輛在羅伯特·S·珊農名下
One of 'em is registered to a Robert S. Shannon,
也就是鮑比·S
A.K.A. Bobby S.
他是斯塔頓島愛爾蘭黑幫的首腦
He's a shot caller for the Irish mob over in Staten Island.
也是個心狠手辣的王八蛋
He's a ruthless son of a bitch, too--
販毒  襲擊他人
drug trafficking, assaults.
他是斯塔頓島內一半兇殺案的嫌疑人
He's suspected of half a dozen murders over in Staten Island.
等一下  偷偷去斯塔頓島
Wait a minute. Secret trips to Staten Island,
和那么多的錢
all that cash...
如果這個蛋糕店是黑幫洗錢的地方呢
What if the cupcake shop is actually a mob front?
蛋糕師吉米·韋蘭
Jimmy Whelan the baker
其實是洗錢師吉米·韋蘭
is actually Jimmy Whelan the money launderer.
鮑比·S可能跟他鬧了別扭
Bobby S. could've had a falling out with him,
所以就把他弄死了
could've whacked him.
也許吧  但我們需要更多的證據
Maybe, but we're gonna need more
不能因為他的車出現在犯罪現場
than just his car at the crime scene
就把他和謀殺連在一起
to connect him to that murder.
也許有人能幫我們
Well, I may have somebody who can help us out with that.
我找出了他的通話記錄
I pulled Jimmy's phone records.
過去三天里  他接到了無數個電話
In the last three days, he received numerous calls
都是一個女人打來的  叫塞...
from a woman named, um... Sibhan...
塞
Siob--
塞博  賽博
Siob--Sib--
-雪芳  -雪芳
- Siobhan. - Siobhan?
愛爾蘭人這點很"出名"
Yeah, the Irish are notorious
喜歡取讀不出來的名字
for spelling names in wild and unpronounceable ways.
我不知道你是怎么念出
I don't even see how you get that from--
我也不知道
You're not alone.
雪芳·奧多
Anyway, Siobhan O'Doul,
她在斯塔頓島開了間酒吧
she runs a bar over in Staten Island.
根據有組織犯罪科記錄顯示
And according to Organized Crime,
那是鮑比·S做生意的地方
it's a place where Bobby S. does a lot of his business.
酒吧是雪芳開的吧
Does Siobhan happen to own that bar?
是的
She does, yeah.
謝謝你能來  奧多女士
Thank you for coming in, Ms. O'Doul.
愿為紐約警察貢獻微薄之力
Anything for New York's finest.
尤其是考慮到
Yeah, especially considering that
像妨礙司法這樣的重罪指控
a felony charge like obstruction
會讓你丟掉酒水販賣許可證
would cost you your liquor license.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我需要從你這了解吉米·韋蘭的情況
I need some answers about Jimmy Whelan.
沒聽過這個人
Never heard of him.
這可有意思了  因為過去三天里
That's funny considering you made seven phone calls
你給他打了七通電話
to him over the last three days.
蛋糕店的吉米
Oh, Jimmy the baker.
我想訂一些紙杯蛋糕
Yeah, I-I'm thinking of ordering some cupcakes.
你沒機會了  他被殺了
Yeah, well, you missed your chance. He was killed.
什么時候
When?
今天的早些時候
Earlier today.
你知道什么情況嗎
Do you know anything about it?
不知道  我怎么會知道
No. Why would I?
我們認為一個經常去你酒吧的人
Well, we think that someone that
和這個案子有聯系
frequents your bar was involved.
關于鮑比·S你知道什么
What can you tell me about Bobby S.?
我不會再多說一個字
I'm not saying another word.
把我的手機給我  我現在就要打電話
Give me my phone call. I want my phone call now.
伙計們
Hey, guys.
怎么了
Hey, what's up, man?
抱歉遲到了
Sorry I'm late.
和...那什么的事怎么樣了
How did the, uh, thing go, with the, uh...
在那啥里那啥
You know, do the thing in the thing
再把那啥給醫生
and give the thing to the doctor?
挺順利的
Yeah. Uh, it went... fine.
你的小泳將們游得快嗎
So are your swimmers swimming?
還不知道呢
Um, I don't know yet.
有案子啊
Hey, caught a case.
是的是的  有個案子
Yeah, yeah, as a matter of fact, we did.
讓我給你科普一下
Let me bring you up to speed.
大伙好
Hi, guys.
你好啊  珍妮
Hey. Hey, what's up, Jenny?
凱文  你沒帶午餐
Kevin, you forgot your lunch.
謝了  寶貝
Thanks, baby.
要是沒了我  你該怎么辦
What would you do without me, huh?
費頓
Fenton?
雪芳
Siobhan?
費頓
Fenton.
你干什么呢
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
這是我老公
That's my husband.
你結婚了
You're married?
女士  不能扇警察的耳光
Oh, lady, you can't slap a cop.
你是警察
You're a cop?
騙子  你這個混蛋
You liar! You son of a bitch!
你怎么能這么做  放開我  放開我
How could you?! Get off of me! Let go!
聽我解釋
I can explain.
靈
書
妙
探
靈
書
妙
探
第五季 第十八集
時間軸：三水  裙帶菜  糖糖
校對：大衛熊  請叫我草海柱    后期&監制：瓜瓜
你們知道這是怎么回事嗎
What do you know about this?
啥都不知道
Not a thing.
拜托
Come on.
咱們的萊恩有沒有可能
Is it possible our Ryan
干出這么狗血的出軌事件呢
is involved in something scandalous and tawdry?
萊恩  不可能  他干不出來
Ryan? No way. He doesn't have it in him.
但是你沒看到
Yeah, but did you see the way
雪芳給他狠狠地一吻嗎
Siobhan gave him that flying lip lock?
他們  看  珍妮生氣了
They--ooh. Look, Jenny's pissed.
這很正常
Yeah, well, it's not surprising
當你發現你的另一半也藏著秘密的時候
when you find out someone you're in a relationship with
你也會生氣
is keeping a secret.
我
I...
淡定  他出來了
Be cool. Here he comes.
自然點  自然點
Act normal. Act normal.
很自然啊
I am. This is normal.
該死
Damn.
鮑比·S
Bobby S.
你們覺得是他
Are we thinking that this guy
除掉了吉米·韋蘭嗎
is the one that took out Jimmy Whelan?
等下  你認識鮑比·S
Wait. You know Bobby S.?
我們以前是朋友
Yeah, we were friends back in the day.
你和這種混蛋是朋友  怎么回事
You were friends with this lowlife? How's that?
我們以前在一個幫派里
We used to run in the same crew.
進兇案組之前
I was undercover for 14 months
我做過14個月的臥底
before I joined homicide.
你在斯塔頓島做過臥底
You were undercover on Staten Island?
在愛爾蘭黑幫
With the Irish mob?
是  關于鮑比·S我們還知道什么
Yeah. So what do we got on Bobby S.?
等等  等等
No. Hold on. Hold on.
繼續前幾句話
Just go back for a second, please.
你在那里臥底
You were undercover?
在那和雪芳...
That's where you and Siobhan used to--
這件事很復雜
It's complicated.
我就喜歡復雜
I love complicated.
雪芳和這件案子有什么關系
How is Siobhan connected to all this?
她認識死者
She knows the vic.
顯然還認識鮑比·S
And she knows Bobby S., obviously.
但她不肯開口合作
But she's not talking.
或許她會愿意告訴我
Maybe she'll talk to me.
我猜你的真名不是費頓·奧康納咯
So I guess it's not Fenton O'Connell.
是凱文  凱文·萊恩
It's Kevin. Kevin Ryan.
至少你是愛爾蘭裔
Well, at least you're Irish.
關于這一點你沒有撒謊
You didn't lie about that.
很多事我都撒謊了
I lied about a lot of things.
他們說你躲起來了
They said you went into hiding.
七年來杳無音信
Seven years without a word.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你什么都不知道
You do not know.
相信我  我也不想走的
Believe me, I didn't want to go.
省省吧
Spare me.
你甚至都沒種當面告訴我
You didn't even have the guts to tell me to my face.
只在梳妝臺上留了一張紙條
Just a note on the dresser.
雪芳  我知道你很生氣
Siobhan, I know you're angry.
但如果你陷入了麻煩
But if you're in trouble,
如果你知道鮑比·S跟兇案有關
if you know something about Bobby S. killing this guy,
告訴我
tell me.
讓我幫你
Let me help you.
你去死吧
You can go straight to hell,
臭條子
Cop.
做臥底
Deep cover?
他居然沒告訴過我
I can't believe he didn't tell me.
埃斯波  他甚至都沒告訴珍妮
Espo, he didn't even tell Jenny.
但我是他的好兄弟  她只是妻子罷了
Yeah, but I'm his best friend. She's just the wife.
就是因為這種思想  你才一直打光棍
Thus proving why there is no Mrs. Esposito.
那是因為很難找到配得上我的女人
Hey, it's hard to find a woman for this much man.
談得怎么樣
So how'd it go?
沒成功
It didn't.
那么
So, uh,
我們推測鮑比殺這家伙的動機是什么
what do we think Bobby's motive was for killing this guy?
我們不知道
We don't know.
但似乎他們為了什么事鬧掰了
But it seems like the two of them had a falling out of some sort.
是啊  可以這么說
Yeah, you could put it that way.
請問你是哪位
And you are?
聯調局特別探員薩姆·沃克
Special agent Sam Walker, FBI.
我是貝克特探長
I'm detective Beckett.
這是萊恩和埃斯波西托警探
This is detective Ryan and Esposito.
萊恩  凱文·萊恩
Ryan? Kevin Ryan?
-你聽說過他  -當然了
- You've heard of him? - Yeah, of course.
這家伙帶著竊聽器潛入愛爾蘭黑幫團伙
This man got inside the Irish mob with a wire
其他人都做不到
when no one else could.
你幫我們抓獲了斯坦頓島上一半的幫派成員
You helped put away half the crew in Staten Island.
只可惜野火燒不盡啊
Too bad the weeds grew back, huh?
他們向來如此
They always do.
聯調局為什么對我們的兇案調查感興趣
So what's the FBI's interest in our murder investigation?
你們的被害人吉米·韋蘭
Your victim--Jimmy Whelan.
他是我的線人
He was my informant.
吉米本來安分地經營著小店
Jimmy was just running his shop,
勉強度日
trying to get by,
但后來經濟嚴重滑坡
but then when the economy turned,
他借了一大筆錢
he borrowed some hard money,
那之后  鮑比·S就控制住他了
And after that, Bobby S. owned him.
那么吉米在向你報告鮑比的生意往來嗎
So Jimmy was feeding you intel on Bobby's operations.
不僅如此
No, more than that.
他本來要幫助我們得到那本幫派"圣經"的
He was gonna help us get the crew's bible.
那本"圣經"
The bible?
我想你們說的一定不是那本圣書吧
I'm guessing we're not talking about the holy book.
不  是幫派成員的叫法
No, it was just something the crew called it.
是一份記載了多年交易和聯絡人的清單
It's a list of transactions and contacts going back years.
拿到那本圣經  就可以扳倒整個犯罪團伙
You get that bible, you'll take down the whole crew.
現在吉米死了  你又得從頭開始了
So now that Jimmy's gone, you're back to square one.
差不多吧  不過我們還有雪芳
Pretty much, though we still have Siobhan.
不好意思   我沒聽明白
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
她也是我的線人
She's my informant, too.
什么  雪芳是不會告密的
What? Siobhan wouldn't snitch.
過去的雪芳或許不會
Maybe not the old Siobhan.
但事實上  你走后
But the truth is, once you left,
她很難過
she fell on hard times.
幫派成員都在她的酒吧喝酒
The crew drinks at her bar.
他們跟她聊天  信任她
They talk to her. They trust her.
鮑比·S甚至在她地下室設了一個辦公室
Bobby S. even keeps an office in the basement.
她想掙脫出來時  我們提出了一項交易
So when she wanted out, we made an offer.
什么交易  證人保護計劃嗎
For what, witness protection?
是的  前提是她幫我們扳倒黑幫
Yeah, if she helps us bring down the crew.
她的出路就是幫我們拿到那本"圣經"
Helping us get the bible, that was gonna be her ticket.
直到鮑比發現吉米是個內奸
Well, until Bobby S. figured out that Jimmy was a rat
并且將他殺害了
and had him killed.
她打電話給吉米就是為這事嗎  提醒他
So that's why she called Jimmy, to warn him?
是的
Yeah.
吉米自認為能說通鮑比
Jimmy thought he could talk his way out of it.
但顯然  他失敗了
Of course, he couldn't.
雪芳現在要怎么辦
So what happens to Siobhan now?
她必須回去
She goes back in.
不行
She can't.
現在不行
Not now. I--
那太危險了
It's too dangerous.
她很清楚要面臨的風險
She knows the risks.
沃克探員  如果我們能發現她和吉米的聯系
Agent Walker, if we linked her to Jimmy,
那鮑比·S也能發現
Then Bobby S. can, too.
聽著  雪芳可以選擇抽身
Look, Siobhan is free to walk away.
去哪呢
And go where?
誰都別想輕易擺脫鮑比·S
You don't just walk away from Bobby S.
大家都知道那一點  他一定不會放過她的
Everybody knows that. He's gonna hunt her down.
你必須把她加入證人保護計劃
You have to put her in witness protection.
拿到"圣經"后當然可以
Yeah, for the bible, sure.
但證人保護計劃不是什么福利項目
But witness protection isn't some entitlement program.
雪芳必須自己爭取
Siobhan has to earn it.
失陪了
Excuse me.
我需要立刻和她見面
I need to meet with her now.
聯調局的人要置她的生死于不顧
The feds are hanging her out to dry.
鮑比一旦發現  肯定會殺了她的
And when Bobby finds out, he'll kill her for sure.
聽著  雪芳
Look, Siobhan,
現在最重要的是不要慌張
The main thing is not to panic.
千萬別做任何可能引起懷疑的事
You don't want to do anything that might arouse suspicion.
低調一段時間  你會沒事的
Just keep your head down for a while. You'll be fine.
不
No.
你會死的
You'll be dead.
瞧瞧你  終于說實話了
Look at you, telling the truth.
那條子說得對  我現在死定了
The cop is right. I'm screwed six ways to sunday here.
鮑比·S把"圣經"放在哪
Where does Bobby S. keep the bible?
在他臥室的保險箱里
In his bedroom safe.
吉米原打算怎么拿到手
How was Jimmy gonna get it?
每周四  鮑比·S會找大伙去賭桌球
Every Thursday, Bobby S. has the guys over to bet on pool.
吉米本該在那時候下手
Jimmy was supposed to do it then.
密碼是多少
What about the combination?
鮑比每周五都會改密碼
Bobby changes it every Friday.
但我知道他的規律
But I know the system he uses.
吉米之所以能拿到圣經
And Jimmy could get the bible
是因為他是幫派成員
because he was one of the crew,
可以進入鮑比·S的房子
and he has access to Bobby S's house.
現在我們在內部沒有人了
And now we got no one inside.
我去
I'll go in.
我去拿那本"圣經"
I'll get the bible.
真的嗎
Really?
你  怎么做
You? How?
你知道我當年跟鮑比·S關系很鐵
You know how close I was to Bobby S. Back then.
我作為費頓·奧康納的身份并沒有暴露
My Fenton O'connell cover is still good.
警探  那是七年前的事了
Detective, that was seven years ago.
幫派成員只知道
As far as the crew knows,
聯調局找上門時我跑了
I bolted when the feds swooped in.
你們還起訴了費頓·奧唐納  對吧
You guys even filed indictments against Fenton O'connell, right?
對
Yeah.
那本圣經我們找了多久了
How long has law enforcement been after that bible,
15年  20年
15, 20 years, huh?
這些家伙是毒瘤
These guys are drug-dealing parasites.
什么時候再有機會把他們一網打盡
When are you gonna get another shot to wipe 'em all out?
聽著  你想要那本圣經
Look, you want the bible,
我們想緝拿兇手鮑比·S
we want Bobby S. for murder,
雪芳想繼續活著
Siobhan wants to keep breathing.
人人獲利
Everybody wins.
我可以做到
I can do this.
我去請示一下上級
Let me run this by my A.S.A.C.
你干什么
What are you doing?
你瘋了嗎
Are you out of your mind?
我當過費頓  我可以重扮一次
I was Fenton. I can be him again.
別為了我丟了性命
Don't get yourself killed on my account.
好吧  你恨我
Okay. Yeah, you hate me.
我知道  我活該
I get that, and I deserve it.
你想得到證人保護嗎
But do you want to be put in witness relocation or not?
想不想
Yes or no?
警探
Detective...
你剛剛說的是認真的嗎
Were you serious about that offer?
你已經很久沒參與行動了  警探
You've been out of it a long time, detective.
組織發生了變化
There's a new hierarchy,
你必須盡快爭取他們的信任
and you're going to have to win them over, fast.
你已經七年沒扮費頓了
Seven years since you were Fenton--
太久了
That's a lifetime.
光扮演還不夠
It's not enough to act like him.
你必須成為這個人
You must become him.
我就是費頓·奧康納
I am Fenton O'connell.
如果你說服不了他們
If you're not convincing,
必死無疑
you're dead.
我就是費頓·奧康納
I am Fenton O'connel.
我不喜歡這樣  兄弟
I don't like this, bro.
你沒戴竊聽器  也沒帶定位器
You don't have a wire, no locator.
如果我戴這些  鮑比·S會發現的
If I did, Bobby S. would find 'em.
只能這樣  伙計
This is the way it's gotta be, man.
那兩個給你擔保的沃克探員的線人
What's the name of Agent Walker's informants
叫什么名字
who will vouch for you?
梅森兄弟  馬特和托尼
The Mason brothers, Matt and Tony.
最近一次在哪蹲的監獄
Where'd you do your last stretch?
埃爾邁拉  殺了一個人
Elmira for man one.
我還能告訴你我的手機號
I can even tell you my cell number.
我心里有數  好嗎
I know what I'm doing, okay?
雪芳呢
What about Siobhan?
我們的計劃沒問題
Our plan is solid.
我能行
I got this.
那回頭見  搭檔
See you on the other side, partner.
怎么  就這么歡迎我嗎
What, this is the welcome I get, huh?
你們這些愛爾蘭混蛋都不想我嗎
None of you Irish bastards missed me, huh?
費頓
Fenton?
費頓·奧康納
Fenton O'connell?
雪芳
Hey, Siobhan.
也很高興見到你  瑪吉
Nice to see you, too, Maggie.
你還想要什么  列隊歡迎嗎
What'd you expect, a parade?
不想想你對雪芳干的混蛋事
After what you did to Siobhan?
你只能打一拳
Unh-unh. One shot's all you get.
放開那位女士
Hey, take your hands off the lady.
只要她別礙著我
Long as she keeps her hands off of me.
七年了  費頓
Seven years, Fenton?
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell have you been?
聽著  你生氣  我懂
Look, you're pissed. I get it.
可這事我們私下解決  好嗎
But we'll work all this... out, maybe a little less publicly.
不過我得先找鮑比·S聊聊
But first I need to talk to Bobby S.
原來你回來是找鮑比的
Oh, that's why you came back, for Bobby?
讓我談好正事
Let me handle my business,
然后我把時間都給你
and then I'll have nothing but time for you.
你可真有魅力
Ah, you are such a charmer.
可如果你要找的是鮑比·S
But if it's Bobby S. you're after,
就得先和他的二把手談
you're gonna have to go through his number two.
是嗎  誰呢
Yeah? Who might that be?
我丈夫
My husband...
連姆
Liam.
跟你說  他不是我認識的萊恩了
I'm telling you, man. He's not the Ryan I know.
我說的不僅是他的發型和著裝
And I'm not just talking about the haircut and the clothes.
他像是變了個人
It's like he's a different dude.
他就該是那樣子
That's what he's supposed to be.
他進入角色了  他是費頓  那很好
He's in character. He's Fenton. That's good.
如果他還不夠好呢
Yeah, but what if he's not good enough?
時隔七年  難免有所生疏
After seven years, he's gotta be rusty.
這些斯坦頓島的家伙可不是吃素的
And these Staten Island boys are no joke.
兩位  幫萊恩最好的方式
You guys, the best way to help Ryan
是給鮑比·S定罪
is by building a case against Bobby S.
可能比我們設想的棘手
That might be trickier than we thought.
鮑比·S的68款突擊者有張電子付費通行卡
Bobby S's '68 Charger has an electronic E-Z Pass,
而且記錄顯示
and records show
突擊者開車去揚克斯
the Charger drove to Yonkers
在上午十點通過喬治·華盛頓橋
via the George Washington Bridge around 10:00 A.M.
下午兩點后才回程
It didn't make the return trip till after 2:00 P.M.
吉米在11點半到12點間遇害
Jimmy was killed between 11:30 and 12:00.
這幫鮑比洗清了嫌疑
That puts Bobby in the clear.
怎么可能
How is that possible?
托德在面包店門口看到的那輛車
The car that Todd saw outside of the bakery
一定是鮑比·S的
had to have been Bobby S's.
或許他想辦法讓電子付費通行卡失效了
Maybe he somehow disabled his E-Z Pass,
制造出他往返揚克斯的假象
making it appear as though all he did was go to and from Yonkers.
即便是這樣  我們怎么證明呢
Okay, yeah, but how do we prove that?
我們查清他在揚克斯期間的去處
We figure out where he went when he was in Yonkers.
然后找證據
And then we find evidence
證明他在死亡時間區離開過那里
that he left during our time-of-death window.
他想制造不在場證明  我們就拆穿他
He's trying to build an alibi, and we're gonna tear it down.
把你手機給我
Give me your phone.
為什么
Why?
鮑比·S向來信不過電子設備
Bobby S. has an abiding distrust of electronic devices.
把你手機給我
Give me your phone.
這不是讓人家生誤會嗎
Whoa. Whoa. What'll the missus think, huh?
鮑比
Hey, Bobby.
我認識你嗎
Do I know you?
搞什么  是我  費頓
What the hell? It's me Fenton.
我記得多年前認識個費頓·奧唐納
I recall knowing a Fenton O'connell years ago.
他待我情同手足
He was like a brother to me.
非常仗義的家伙
Real stand-up guy...
直到他跑路了
Till he cut and ran.
別這樣  鮑比
Come on, Bobby.
我被出賣了  你知道的
I got ratted out. You know that.
我要留下來
Me hanging around
只會給大家都惹麻煩
woulda just brought more heat down on everyone.
所以你就人間蒸發了
So you made yourself scarce.
實際上  這七年里沒人有你的音訊
In fact, no one's heard from you in... seven years.
你去哪里了
Where you been?
西部
Out west.
四處干了點小打小鬧
Been making some moves here and there
直到過了訴訟時效
until the statute of limitations ran out.
老實說  鮑比
Tell you the truth, Bobby,
我要是手里沒有好貨
I didn't want to come home till I had something
都不好意思回來
to bring to the table.
朋友
Well, friend...
拿出來吧
Here's the table.
我聽說聯調局抓走了本·吉迪恩
I heard the feds took down Ben Gideon,
你可能需要一些貨源
so you might be in need of some product.
我一直和梅森兄弟在芝加哥外奔波
I been working with the Mason brothers out of Chicago.
我聽說過他們
I've heard of 'em.
這是穩定的貨源  質量也不錯
It's a stable source, quality stuff.
我可以幫你弄到一切你想要的
I can get you whatever you need.
我在擴展銷路  鮑比
This is me stepping up, Bobby.
那又怎樣
So what...
你就是歌里唱到的漂泊者
You're the wild rover from the song?
"滿載著黃金而歸"  是這個吧
"Returning with gold in great store," is that it?
要么你就是奸細
Or are you a rat?
你知道我不是這種人
You know me better than that.
這個嘛
Well...
該說的我都說了  我不會求你的  鮑比
I said my piece, but I'm not gonna beg, Bobby.
看你的了  好嗎
It's up to you, okay?
是的  沒錯
Oh, yeah, it is.
那么
So...
我是應該歡迎浪子回家呢
Should I welcome home the prodigal son,
還是讓連姆把子彈
or should I have Liam put a bullet
射進你的后腦
in the back of your head?
等著你下令呢  鮑比
Oh, just say the word, Bobby.
你要是覺得我是奸細
You think I'm some kind of rat,
一個不正直的人
that I'm a man without honor?
那就動手吧
Then you pull the trigger.
要是你懷疑我  鮑比
You doubt me, Bobby,
那你就親自動手吧
you do it yourself.
費頓回來了
Fenton's back.
歡迎回家
Welcome home.
還在這呢
Still here.
要喝點什么
What can I get you?
一品脫黑啤酒
A pint of the black stuff.
請大家舉杯
Glasses in the air.
盧克 15:32
Luke 15:32.
這算哪門子祝酒詞啊
What the hell kind of a toast is that?
你在哪找到這傻帽的  鮑比
Where'd you find this heathen, Bobby?
他在主日學校讀過書嗎
Didn't he ever go to sunday school?
我在這歡喜地慶祝
"We should celebrate and rejoice
是因為
because..."
因為你在這的弟兄
"Because your brother here was dead
死而復生了
and has come to life."
歡迎回家
Welcome home.
-為了費頓  -費頓
- To Fenton. - Fenton.
一切安好
Slainte.
你怎么看他的
What do you think of him?
我怎么看無所謂  要看鮑比·S
Doesn't matter what I think. It's up to Bobby S.
是啊  可你相信他說的
Yeah, but do you buy his story
這七年他都在哪的故事嗎
about where he's been for the last seven years?
我不知道  但我會去調查的
I don't know, but I'm gonna check it out.
要是他說謊了呢
And if he's lying about somethin'?
那我就殺了這個混蛋
Then I'll kill the bastard.
我想我知道鮑比·S去了揚克斯什么地方
So I think I figured out where Bobby S went in Yonkers.
去了跑馬場
The Raceway.
他在那里的取款機取了500美元
He pulled out $500 in cash from the A.T.M. there.
去賭馬了
Betting on the ponies.
停車場里有監控嗎
Any security cameras in the parking lot?
埃斯波正在查  要是我們能證明
Espo's checking right now, but if we can prove
他恰好在案發時間離開
that he left just before our time-of-death window,
那就幫我們給他定罪了
then that should help us nail him for the murder.
不用了  謝謝  我很好
Oh, no. Thank you. I'm fine.
我們有萊恩的消息嗎
So do we know how Ryan's doing?
沒有  我討厭有事情發生我卻不知道
I don't know, and I hate not knowing things.
好吧  聽著
Okay, look. Uh...
喬丹不是女的  行了嗎
Jordan is not a woman, all right?
那他是誰啊  或者是什么啊
Then who is it? Or rather, what is it?
這重要嗎
Why does it matter?
因為  卡塞爾  對你很重要
Because, Castle, it matters to you.
你就不能告訴我嗎
Why won't you tell me?
蕾妮確定吉米·韋蘭身上纖維的來源了
Lanie's identified the fibers on Jimmy Whelan.
是澳大利亞的羊毛制品
They are... wool from an Australian sheep.
也許鮑比有幫手
Ah, perhaps Bobby's had an accomplice--
一只冷血兇惡的綿羊
a cold-blooded, murderous sheep.
-就是這個  -真的假的
- That's it. - Seriously?
不是那個  看這個
No, not that. This. Look.
看他穿的外套
Look at the jacket he's wearing.
是皮革的
It's leather shearling...
上面有羊毛
with wool.
-這就和謀殺案聯系起來了  -別急
- That ties him to the murder. - Not so fast.
跑道的貴賓停車區區
There were no cameras in the V.I.P. parking area
沒有監控
of the racetrack.
但那天是鮑比·S的幸運日
But it turns out Bobby S had a lucky day.
40比1的概率他都贏了  賺了一萬四
His 40-to-1 long shot won. Netted him 14 grand.
他穿著同一件外套
And wearing the same coat.
問題是
The problem is,
他填交稅表格的時間
he's filling out his w-2g tax forms
與吉米被殺的時間一致
at the exact same time that Jimmy got whacked.
那鮑比就不可能是兇手了
Then Bobby can't be our killer.
他是被陷害的
So he was being set up.
有人借了鮑比·S的車  留下那些纖維
Someone borrowed Bobby S's car, planed those fibers,
這就是為了讓他當替罪羊
All in an effort to make him look like the killer.
要是有人陷害鮑比
If someone's trying to set Bobby up,
萊恩就必須知道這一點
Ryan needs to know.
你知道這么見面很危險
You know... it's risky meeting like this.
最好是有重要的事
It better be important.
吉米不是鮑比殺的
Bobby didn't kill Jimmy.
真正的兇手偷了他的車然后陷害他
The real killer stole his car and set him up.
或者是鮑比命令別人做的
Or Bobby ordered the hit
把車借給了兇手
And loaned his car to the killer.
不是的  老兄
No, bro.
現場的證據是特意留下的
Forensic evidence was purposefully left behind.
這是陷害
It's a frame.
很可能就是他幫派里的人
Probably someone in his own crew.
好的  我會留心的
Okay. I'll keep my eyes open.
這對你有什么好處啊
What good is that gonna do you, hmm?
一旦那邊發生了什么事  我不在你身邊
What good is that gonna do you when something goes down,
這對你有什么好處啊
I'm not there to back you up?
你要做的就是放任不管
What you need to do is walk away.
等完事了我再離開
I'll walk away when I'm done.
你想什么呢
What's wrong with you?
你根本輸不起 哥們  你有珍妮
You got a lot to lose, man. You got Jenny.
你還準備要個孩子
You're trying to start a family.
用不著你告訴我這有多危險
I don't need you to tell me what's at stake here.
聽著
Look, man...
鮑比邀請我今晚和他去打臺球
I got invite to Bobby's pool game tonight.
就等這個呢
This is it.
這是我拿到圣經的機會
This is my shot at getting that bible.
這不值得啊  伙計
It's not worth it, man.
到手了我就給你打電話
I'll call you when I get it.
鮑比怎么可能不是兇手
How could bobby is not be the killer?
我聽他親口說覺得吉米是奸細
I heard him say he thought jimmy was a rat.
肯定別人也聽到了
Someone else must've heard that, too.
幫派里的人嗎
Someone in the crew?
肯定是這樣  對吧
It has to be, right?
這太糟了  你今晚不能去打臺球了
This is bad. You can't go to the pool game tonight.
我必須去
I have to go.
我不會再有別的機會了
I won't get another chance.
這也是你唯一的機會
You won't get another chance.
鮑比保險箱的密碼是多少
What's the combination to Bobby's safe?
3-0-4-2-1-7.
304217  你怎么知道的
3-0-4-2-1-7. How do you know that?
周五晚上鮑比會叫我打電話給他
Bobby has me ring up a total on the cash register
告訴他收銀機里錢的總數
on friday nights.
他用總款數當做密碼
He bases the combination on that total.
我們會順利度過這一關的
We're gonna get through this.
不是吧  你還留著這個小家伙
Oh, come on. You still have this little guy?
等等  它叫什么名字來著
Wait. Um, what his name again?
你怎么能忘了胡子先生呢
How could you forget Mr. Whiskers?
你花了50刀才幫我贏回了他
You spent over 50 bucks trying to win him for me.
那個套圈游戲太坑爹了
That ring toss was a bitch.
但他物有所值
Well, it was worth every penny.
他陪伴我度過了不少難關
He's seen me through some pretty rough times.
我們的過去沒有一點是真的嗎
Was any of it real?
我對你的感情是真的
What I felt was.
我得走了
I gotta go.
今晚至關重要
Big night tonight.
在揚克斯跑馬場的調查
So the canvass at Yonkers raceway
有了新發現
came up with something.
泊車員見過鮑比·S的黑色道奇車
A parking attendant saw Bobby S's black charger.
車子在案發半小時后返回
Now it returned 30 minutes after the murder.
他只是遠遠地看到了  但他說
He only saw it from a distance, but he says the driver
司機帶著一頂棒球帽
Was wearing a baseball cap,
隨后他步行去了地鐵站
and he walked to the subway stop.
聯系一下紐約交管局
Okay, let's touch base with the M.T.A.
聯系過了
Already did.
我參照了那段時間里所有消費過的地鐵卡
I cross-referenced all metrocards swiped at that time.
有一張是用信用卡購買的
One of them was bought with a credit card,
信用卡的主人是連姆·芬奇
and that credit card belonged to Liam Finch.
他是鮑比·S的二把手
That's Bobby S's number two.
這是一場陰謀
It's a coup.
連姆設計陷害鮑比來上位
Liam is framing Bobby to get him out of the way.
他想要掌權
He wants to take over.
而萊恩正好插手了這件事
And Ryan walked right in the middle of it.
不止如此  他不僅插手了
Worse. He didn't walk in the middle.
而且以鮑比·S朋友的身份攪局
He walked in as Bobby S's friend.
他自然成為了連姆的敵人
That makes him Liam's enemy.
我們得提醒他
Okay, we have to warn him.
如果我們打給他  他的身份就暴露了
If we call him, we could blow his cover.
如果不打電話  他會被殺的
If we don't, he could end up dead.
不是吧你
Get the hell outta here.
你的臺球什么時候打得這么好了
Since when'd you become such a pool hustler?
請叫我"快桿艾迪"
Just call me Fast Eddie.
過來
Come here.
我看了你的報價  我能接受
I went over your numbers. I can live with 'em.
你多久能把貨從芝加哥運過來
So how soon can you get some of that Chicago crank up here?
到這周末  我能弄到五磅
I can get you 5 pounds by this weekend.
下周的話
Come next week,
你想要多少  我就有多少
I can get you however much you want.
棒極了
Love it.
到你了  走狗屎運的混蛋
Take your shot, you lucky bastard.
基恩的電話  說有急事
It's Keane. Says it's urgent.
基恩  怎么了
Yeah, Keane.
連姆  你說得對
Liam, you were right.
有奸細
We got a rat in the house.
待會兒打給你
I'll call you back.
他說我們之中有奸細
He said we got a rat in the house.
好啦  我要去上廁所
All right, I gotta hit the head.
叫史迪威把車開到前門
Tell Stevie to bring my car around front.
體育干將  我正找你呢
Hey,sport. Been looking for you.
鮑比·S叫我們開車兜兜風
Bobby S needs us to take a ride.
好的  我去拿下手機
Okay. Let me get my phone.
你用不上手機
You're not gonna be needing it.
車子就在外面  你負責開車
Car's out back. You're driving.
好吧  我去去就來
All right. I'll be right back.
該走了  費頓
Time to go... Fenton.
萊恩還是不接電話
Ryan's still not answering.
如果鮑比·S不讓人用手機
Well,if Bobby S doesn't allow cell phones in his presence,
那他可能還在和萊恩打臺球
maybe he and Ryan are still just playing pool.
沃克特工說了什么
What did Agent Walker say?
聯邦政府也不清楚萊恩在哪兒
The Feds don't know any more than we do about where Ryan is.
事情不太對勁
Something's not right.
凱文遇到危險了嗎
Guys... Is Kevin in trouble?
沒有
Uh, no.
我們只是在討論些辦案程序上的事
We're just talking some procedural stuff.
別騙我了  哈維  到底怎么了
Don't lie to me, Javi. What's going on?
我丈夫呢
Where's my husband?
珍妮  我們邊喝咖啡邊聊吧
Jenny, maybe we should go get a coffee.
那么你們不知道他在哪兒
So you don't know where he is?
是的  但是我們會找到他的
No. But we are going to find him.
我們認為他并沒有遇到什么大危險
And,um,we don't believe that he's in any immediate danger.
他為什么要這樣做
Why would he do a thing like this?
他可能是想證明些什么
Maybe he thinks he has something to prove
因為我的...懷孕問題
'Cause of all of our... pregnancy stuff.
我覺得其中有很多原因
You know,I think that there are probably a number of reasons,
但主要原因是  他想做對的事
But the main one is that he just wants to do the right thing.
那才是他  那是他當警察的原因
I mean,that's who he is, that's why he became a cop,
那正是你愛上他的原因
That's why you fell in love with him.
我只想他平安回來
I just want him to come home.
貝克特  我有話跟你說
Hey,Beckett. I need to talk to you.
我們要去碼頭嗎
We going to the docks?
在碼頭只有兩件事可做
Only two things to do at the docks--
殺人或是釣魚
Kill someone or go fishing.
現在釣魚有點晚了  不是嗎
Kinda late to be fishing,ain't it?
是的  魚兒都睡著了
Yep. All the fishies are asleep.
什么情況
What now,huh?
我一直對你有所懷疑
You know,I had my suspicions about you
自你踏進雪芳的酒吧的那刻起
from the moment you walked into Siobhan's bar.
可每個人都說費頓是純爺們
But,no. Everybody said,"Fenton is stand-up. "
大家都相信你  包括鮑比·S
Everybody vouched for you,even Bobby S.
但你仍然懷疑我  是吧
But you still had your doubts,huh?
是的
That's right.
所以今天我讓基恩跟蹤你
So I had Keane follow you around today.
我知道我們之中有個奸細
You know,I knew that we had a rat amongst us.
但是我不明白的是
But what I didn't figure
他是怎么在我們眼皮子底下偽裝的
was how that rat could hide in plain sight.
-雪芳  -對不起
- Siobhan? - I'm sorry.
我也是  兄弟
So am I,brother.
基恩跟著你去了雪芳的家
Keane followed you over to Siobhan's place.
是的  我和她的鄰居聊天
Yeah,I spoke with one of her neighbors.
發現她兩天前被警察抓住了
Turns out she was picked up by the cops two days ago.
基恩很好奇  所以闖進了她家
Being an inquisitive lad,Keane broke in to her place.
告訴他你的發現吧  基恩
Tell him what you found,Keane.
我翻了她的手機記錄  費頓
I went through her cell phone,Fenton.
伙計  她曾和聯邦調查局通過話
Man,she's been talking to the FBI.
這一切無疑是她搗的鬼
After all this time, nothing but a snitch.
猶大的內心
A judas...
天使的臉龐
With an angel's face.
費頓  你知道的  我很講求公平
Now,Fenton,you know me. I'm nothing if not fair.
因此我給你一個公平的機會
So I'm gonna give you a fair chance
來證明你與此事無關
to prove you knew nothing about this.
打得她腦袋開花
Blow her brains out.
費頓  今晚不是她死
Fenton,we're leaving with one
就是你們一起死
or two bodies tonight.
全看你的說
It's up to you.
沒關系的  我不怪你
It's okay. It's not your fault.
開槍吧
Just do it.
我做不到  鮑比
I just can't do it, Bobby.
我不能打死她
I can't shoot her.
但是我能夠打死你
However I have no problem shooting you.
空彈匣  賤人
Empty. You son of a bitch.
以防萬一  兄弟
Had to be sure, friend.
該死的  我對你太失望了  費頓
And damn. I'm so disappointed in you, Fenton.
你還會更失望的
Not as disappointed as you're about to be.
我的真名不是費頓
My name's not Fenton.
而是凱文·萊恩
It's Kevin Ryan,
我是警察
And I'm a cop.
什么  你是警察
What? A cop?
沒錯  而且我要逮捕你們三個
Yeah, and I'm placing the three of you under arrest.
想得美
Well, that'll be a hell of a trick,
考慮到連姆馬上就要崩了你和你的女友
considering Liam's about to shoot you... and your girlfriend.
等等  連姆  先別動手
Wait a second. Liam, before you do that,
我先問你個問題  你的手機在哪兒
let me ask you a question. Where's your cell phone, huh?
什么
What?
還記得我們在大廳扭打的時候嗎
Remember when we tussled back in the hall?
沒錯  我掏了你口袋
Yeah. I picked your pocket.
然后趁你不注意的時候
And then when you weren't looking,
我打給了我的搭檔  讓電話一直通著
I dialed my partner and left the line open.
不可能
No way.
我們要去哪兒  他聽得清清楚楚
He heard exactly where we were going.
-連姆  -他在胡說  鮑比
- Liam. - He's full of crap, Bobby.
-他是嚇唬我們  -是嗎
- He's bluffing. - Oh, am I?
要不我們見見我的搭檔吧
Why don't we meet my partner, huh?
喂  哈維爾  你在哪兒
Yo, Javi, where you at?!
我在這兒  哥們
Right here, bro.
別輕舉妄動  他當過特種兵
No, no. He is former special forces.
你們不是他的對手
You do not want to draw on him.
還想見見其他伙伴嗎
Want to meet the rest of my crew?
嘿  貝克特
Hey, Beckett!
萊恩  是你打的電話嗎
You called, Ryan?
小子  別被她的美貌騙了
Don't let the looks fool you, boys.
你們也不是她的對手
You don't want to mess with her, either.
卡塞爾
Castle!
不是吧  我沒穿防彈衣呢
Seriously? I didn't... I didn't bring my vest.
放下武器  快
Drop your weapons. Now.
我有全紐約最好的律師
I got the best lawyer in New York.
我會被無罪釋放的
I'm gonna walk.
聯調局有了這個你跑不了
Not when I hand the Feds this.
一看這華麗麗的西裝三件套就知道
Snazzy 3-piece suit could only mean one thing...
萊恩回來了
Ryan is back.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
連姆審得怎樣了
So where are we with Liam?
貝克特正在審呢  想讓他承認
Beckett's got him in the box, trying to get him to confess
自己殺了吉米·韋蘭
to Jimmy Whelan's murder.
沃克探員來電說  那本圣經真是好東西
And Agent Walker called. He said the bible you gave him is gold.
鮑比·S和他的同伙們都完蛋了
Bobby S and his whole crew are doing down.
哈維爾
And, uh, Javi...
那天在餐館
The other day at the diner--
沒事兒  當時那不是你本人
Don't sweat it. That wasn't you talkin', man.
那是費頓
That was Fenton.
謝謝理解
Yeah. Thanks.
你們一定不信  但連姆確實不是兇手
You guys aren't gonna believe this, But Liam is not our killer.
你說什么  可那確實是他的地鐵卡啊
What are you talking about? It was his MetroCard.
他是用自己的信用卡付錢的
He paid for it with his own credit card,
他從鮑比車上下來后刷過卡
And then he swiped it after he dropped off Bobby's car.
我知道  但他有不在場證明
I know, but his alibi is solid.
他當時在斯塔頓島
He was on Staten Island at that time.
如果他有不在場證明
Okay, well, if he has a solid alibi,
唯一的問題就是
the only question that remains is,
誰能拿到他的地鐵卡
who had access to his MetroCard?
瑪吉
Maggie...
我覺得你能干出很多事  但不會去殺人
You know, I pegged you for a lot of things, never a killer.
是啊  我也沒想到你會是個緝毒大隊長
Yeah, I pegged you for a lot of things, but never a narc.
其實我是兇殺案警探
Actually, see, I'm a homicide detective,
所以我知道你殺了烘焙師吉米
which is why I know that you killed Jimmy the Baker.
什么吉米
Jimmy the who?
老天  你還要和我們玩下去嗎
Oh, god. Are we actually gonna play this game?
不早了  我都累了
It's late. I am tired.
警察搜了你家  找到了你的槍
Officers went through your house, And they found your gun.
和射殺吉米的槍口徑一致
Same caliber that killed Jimmy.
遲早我們會查出兩支槍彈道一致
It's only a matter of time before we get a ballistics match.
這么說  連姆不知道他老婆做了什么
So Liam had no idea what his wife was doing?
對  都是瑪吉干的
No, it was all Maggie.
她知道連姆忠心耿耿
She knew that Liam was too loyal,
她覺得只有她把鮑比·S送進監獄
and she figured that if she could get Bobby S in prison,
她丈夫才能稱王
her husband would ascend to the throne.
看來瑪吉就像《麥克白》里的麥克白夫人
So really, lady Maggie was lady Macbeth,
不過她是愛爾蘭人  不是蘇格蘭人
only she was Irish, not Scottish.
凱特  說起喬丹
Listen, Kate, about Jordan...
如果你不想說的話  就別說了
You know what? If, uh, if you don't want to talk about it--
我想談  不過
No, I-I-I wanna, but...
如果你不喜歡你看到的會怎樣
What happens if you don't like what you see?
如果你不讓我看到會怎樣
What happens if you don't let me look?
喬丹汽車公司  在1916到1931年間生產汽車
Jordan Motor Company. They made cars from 1916 to 1931.
這就是喬丹  所謂的大秘密  一家倒閉的公司
That's Jordan? That's the big secret, A defunct car company?
算是吧  這得追溯到我在寄宿學校上學的時候
Sort of. It goes back to my boarding school days.
那是第一個學期  我差點兒被退學
My first semester there, I was in danger of flunking out.
我期末考必須拿A
I needed an "A" on my term paper.
所以你就圍繞那家公司寫了篇文章
So you wrote the paper on that car company?
不  是別人寫的
No. Someone else did,
然后我給了他250美元
and I paid him $250.
卡塞爾  這是你小時候的事
Um, Castle, that happened when you were a kid.
我沒搞懂這怎么改變我對你的看法了
I don't understand why that would change how I see you.
因為它改變我對自己的看法了
Because it changed how I saw myself.
老師在班上讀了我的文章
The teacher read the paper to the entire class
當成了優秀范文  大家為我鼓了掌
as an example of great writing, and they applauded.
那是我第一次被表揚
It was the first time I was celebrated ev--for anything,
但卻是個謊言
And... it was a fraud.
我是個騙子
I... I was a fraud.
從那時起  我開始學寫作
That's when I learned how to write.
我寫啊寫
I wrote and wrote,
努力讓自己成為大家稱贊的那個人
trying to be as great as everyone thought I was...
努力贏取稱贊
trying to earn that applause.
我現在仍在努力
I'm still trying.
你說得對  卡塞爾  這確實改變了我的看法
You're right, Castle. It does change how I see you.
讓我更喜歡你了一點點
It makes me like you just a little bit more.
別忘了胡子先生
Don't forget Mr. Whiskers.
你現在倒是記得他的名字了
Oh, so now you remember his name.
能讓我倆聊會兒嗎
Could you give us a second, please?
我正惦記著你能不能來呢
I was hoping you'd come.
這回我得道個別
I wanted to say good-bye this time.
道別讓我覺得以后再見不到你了
"Good-bye" makes me feel like I'll never see you again.
確實啊
You won't.
明天  你就會到一個新的城市  有個新的名字
Tomorrow you'll be in a new city, have a new name.
你會重新開始
You'll get to start over again.
為什么你要這么做  為我冒生命危險
Why'd you do this, risk your life for me?
你知道的
You know why.
這個叫凱文·萊恩的家伙
This Kevin Ryan guy,
真希望再早點認識他
I wish I would've met him sooner.
對不起  珍妮
I'm sorry, Jenny.
我知道這對你不公平
I know it wasn't fair to you.
告訴我真相
Just tell me the truth.
你做臥底的生活結束了嗎
Is this part of your life, this undercover part, over?
-是啊  結束了  -好
- Yeah, it is now. - Good.
因為我要知道你會在我身邊
Because I need to know that you're gonna be here.
我要知道自己能依靠你
A-and I need to know that I can depend on you,
尤其是因為
Especially after the test results
產科醫生給我們的檢查結果
we got back from the fertility doctor.
-不  壞消息嗎  -是啊
- Oh, no. Bad news? - Yeah.
我們做那檢查真是瞎折騰一場
We took all those damn tests for nothing.
我已經懷孕了
I'm already pregnant.
你懷孕了
You're pregnant?
You're pregnant.
我們開香檳吧
Let's, uh, let's pop some champagne.
不行  我們不能喝香檳
No. We can't pop any champagne
你知道的  因為
You know why...because...
-你懷孕了  -我懷孕了
- You're pregnant. - I'm pregnant.